<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Zigzaggery</title>
    <link>https://zigzaggery.space/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Zigzaggery</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://zigzaggery.space/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Weeknotes 13 - 19 January 2025</title>
      <link>https://zigzaggery.space/post/2025/jan/weeknotes-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zigzaggery.space/post/2025/jan/weeknotes-19/</guid>
      <description>For some reason this was a week dominated by irritability&amp;hellip;&#xA;&amp;hellip;and I&amp;rsquo;m not absolutely sure why. It might have something to do with wanting to feel I&amp;rsquo;m improving my golf game (but still only managing to play well for half any given round).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weeknotes 6 - 12 January 2025</title>
      <link>https://zigzaggery.space/post/2025/jan/weeknotes-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zigzaggery.space/post/2025/jan/weeknotes-12/</guid>
      <description>A week in which it turned out that watching golf (ie walking the course with the players) is just as tiring physically as playing golf&amp;hellip;&#xA;This week there was a professional competition at my club, so I got the chance to play another great local course for free (because we get offered alternative tee times elsewhere when we can&amp;rsquo;t access our own course).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weeknotes 30 December 2024 - 5 January 2025</title>
      <link>https://zigzaggery.space/post/2025/jan/weeknotes-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zigzaggery.space/post/2025/jan/weeknotes-05/</guid>
      <description>The first of the new look weeknotes as we move into the new year&amp;hellip;&#xA;Three walks this week, plus &amp;ldquo;a good walk spoiled&amp;rdquo; (ie a game of golf, as in the quotation commonly misattributed to Mark Twain).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Re-visioning weeknotes</title>
      <link>https://zigzaggery.space/post/2025/jan/re-visioning-weeknotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zigzaggery.space/post/2025/jan/re-visioning-weeknotes/</guid>
      <description>Entering the new year with a new plan for weeknotes&amp;hellip;&#xA;Although I enjoyed writing my first few weeknote instalments last year, they got harder (or less pleasurable?) to write each week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s with the weeknotes?</title>
      <link>https://zigzaggery.space/post/2024/dec/whats-with-the-weeknotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zigzaggery.space/post/2024/dec/whats-with-the-weeknotes/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been just over a month since I left my permanent job, so it&amp;rsquo;s early days in the rest of my life&amp;hellip;&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;ve been writing weeknotes since my last week at work, which is something unexpected (for me, as someone who doesn&amp;rsquo;t write easily and has never managed to keep a diary for more than a few days) maybe that deserves some explanation, as I put a bit more thought into this website, why I decided to post weeknotes at all and how to keep going with this (and other writing).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weeknotes 23 - 29 December 2024</title>
      <link>https://zigzaggery.space/post/2024/dec/weeknotes-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zigzaggery.space/post/2024/dec/weeknotes-29/</guid>
      <description>Christmas is normally only celebrated in our house with food and drink, but this year we got the new lights out and decorated the owl with my Christmas golf outfit hat&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weeknotes 16 - 22 December 2024</title>
      <link>https://zigzaggery.space/post/2024/dec/weeknotes-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zigzaggery.space/post/2024/dec/weeknotes-22/</guid>
      <description>The frangipanis are flowering and it&amp;rsquo;s getting hotter more regularly now, so planning what to do and when is getting more important&amp;hellip;&#xA;Those plans for blogposts other than weeknotes are still just plans, so the frangipani flowers are the image of the week rather than gracing a post about the garden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weeknotes 9 - 15 December 2024</title>
      <link>https://zigzaggery.space/post/2024/dec/weeknotes-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zigzaggery.space/post/2024/dec/weeknotes-15/</guid>
      <description>A week where I got some worthwhile things done, but also went onto campus and back to (unpaid) thinking and writing work too soon&amp;hellip;&#xA;Although I&amp;rsquo;m planning a post (or series of posts) about plants and the garden, I did promise pictures of the Echinopsis oxygona cactus flowers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weeknotes 2 - 8 December 2024</title>
      <link>https://zigzaggery.space/post/2024/dec/weeknotes-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zigzaggery.space/post/2024/dec/weeknotes-08/</guid>
      <description>Still trying to settle into my new life. I did manage to get a few things done while also trying to chill out (and avoid feeling like I have to do all the things all at once)&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weeknotes 24 November - 01 December 2024</title>
      <link>https://zigzaggery.space/post/2024/dec/weeknotes-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zigzaggery.space/post/2024/dec/weeknotes-01/</guid>
      <description>My second weeknotes post - the first week of not working (not being on holiday, just not working) but with some work (which would not surprise anyone that knows me)&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weeknotes 17-23 November 2024</title>
      <link>https://zigzaggery.space/post/2024/nov/weeknotes-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zigzaggery.space/post/2024/nov/weeknotes-24/</guid>
      <description>My first ever weeknotes post following a momentous week - finishing up my work as a Senior Lecturer&amp;hellip;&#xA;I took this image of an iron steer decorating a gate on the way back from a long-planned beach walk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Communicating with Robots and Bots</title>
      <link>https://zigzaggery.space/post/2024/sep/communicating-with-robots-and-bots/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zigzaggery.space/post/2024/sep/communicating-with-robots-and-bots/</guid>
      <description>Originally published in 2019 on my old blog, this post has been updated in 2024 to recognise the continued presence of the MOOC Communicating with Robots and Bots&amp;hellip;&#xA;One of the most enjoyable pieces of writing (and collating of research, videos, news articles, images etc) about robots I have done occurred back in 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still not sure about the card style for this site</title>
      <link>https://zigzaggery.space/post/2024/sep/still-not-sure/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zigzaggery.space/post/2024/sep/still-not-sure/</guid>
      <description>While I know there are lots of sites around the web that are styled using a card type layout, I think that I was probably most influenced by Will Buckingham&amp;rsquo;s blog&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating a new website...</title>
      <link>https://zigzaggery.space/notes/2020/change/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zigzaggery.space/notes/2020/change/</guid>
      <description>Creating this site takes time. I&amp;rsquo;m being impatient and really I need to slow down to enjoy the process (and make fewer little mistakes that mean re-doing things time and time again)!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notes on creating this site</title>
      <link>https://zigzaggery.space/post/2024/sep/notes-on-creating-this-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zigzaggery.space/post/2024/sep/notes-on-creating-this-site/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m creating this site using a theme that I am customising in small ways as I go. While I&amp;rsquo;m building I&amp;rsquo;m just using GitHub Pages as a server for the site.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Which commercial social network to leave first?</title>
      <link>https://zigzaggery.space/notes/2020/change2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zigzaggery.space/notes/2020/change2/</guid>
      <description>One of the reasons I find it difficult to teach Digital and Social Media is that I&amp;hellip; well&amp;hellip; pretty much hate all the commercial social networks now. The first I&amp;rsquo;ll backburner properly will probably be Facebook.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropomorphism and its Discontents</title>
      <link>https://zigzaggery.space/collections/2024/anthropomorphism-chapter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zigzaggery.space/collections/2024/anthropomorphism-chapter/</guid>
      <description>Introduction AI technologies raise many ethical questions. Some of these are associated with technical underpinnings and operation; surveillance, data gathering, and analysis, or copyright and intellectual property issues as can be seen in the widescale processing of published writing or artworks that support generative AI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Note 3</title>
      <link>https://zigzaggery.space/notes/2020/change3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zigzaggery.space/notes/2020/change3/</guid>
      <description>Journaling is not just a little thing you do to pass the time, to write down your memories—though it can be—it’s a strategy that has helped brilliant, powerful and wise people become better at what they do.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robots and Communication</title>
      <link>https://zigzaggery.space/collections/2024/robots-and-communication/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zigzaggery.space/collections/2024/robots-and-communication/</guid>
      <description>Overview Robots and Communication examines human-robot interactions as models of communication. Robots are intriguing communicators because they are created in such a variety of forms. Some are built to appear humanlike, while others are not humanlike in any way, with many different designs existing in the continuum between these extremes.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
